Okay, here's what you need to know about Justin Pearson's path to reinstatement.
Shelby County Commission will meet to decide whether or not to reappoint him
to represent his district here in Tennessee.
Nine of the 13 county commissioners are Democrats.
They hold a super majority on the county commission,
which means that things should go smoothly for him, but there are a few snags.
For starters, I spoke to Commissioner Sugarman today,
and she told me that two of the Democratic commissioners are out of town and won't be voting.
She also shared that she and other commissioners are worried about Tennessee Republicans retaliating.
That if the commission sends Justin Pearson back to the state's Capitol,
that Republicans may make them pay. Literally.
She's concerned that the Tennessee GOP will revoke funding for infrastructure and medical facilities.
It's unclear whether or not those concerns will materialize.
The Republican Speaker of the House has explicitly denied them,
but one thing is for sure, the nation will be watching how this vote plays out.